Guide to the Susan Christopherson papers, circa 1983-2016.
Christopherson, Susan papers,
- Series II. Research
  - Hatch Project Data, etc., 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Economic resilience notes, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Hutton paper, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Reasearch notes, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Media Acad articles, 2000-2004 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Media work force, 2002-2004 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Cornell University paper, 2007-01-04 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Greem economy research 1 of 5, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Greem economy research 2 of 5, 2006-04 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Greem economy research 3 of 5, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Greem economy research 4 of 5, 2006-2007-04 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Greem economy research 5 of 5, 2008-06 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Articles, 2005-2007 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper clippings and magazine, 2009-2014 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Misc. journal articles, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Chapter one: Introduction to critical theory of runaway production draft, Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Book proposal draft The Squeeze, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Research agenda for book, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Book draft editing references, Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Here-one-day-gone-the-next-day: relations of tourism, peripatetic film, production, and place, Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Manuscript notes and varia, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - 21 century jobs trust fund programs audit report, 2007-09 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Contributor agreement, 2009-11-27 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Notes and drafts, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Other resources, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Gerald Berek notes, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Belger regulations, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Corporate restructuring clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Capelli P., rethinking employment, Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Charkham notes, Undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Henry Ergas, tech policy, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Entrepreneurship: under forty group, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Darbishire and Katz: Converging divergences, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Victor Nee and Paul Ingram, noted, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Hodgson, Variety of Capitalism, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Pontusson and Swenson, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - European comparison conference, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Misc. notes and reviews, Undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Forty below draft report, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - European union flex issues, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - References, Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Jeffrey Madrick Tech, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Labor flex Japan, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Media concentration, 2004-07 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Misc. notes and papers, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - New York City, 2003-08 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - NYFTCI Interview info, 2004-12-01 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Entertainment labor, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - News clippings media, 1999-2005 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Canada, 2004-08 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Canada interviews, 2005-03 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Incentive/subsidy info, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Production subsidies, 2003-02 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Vertical integration, 2004-01-28 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Assorted notes, 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Media location trends, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - NYFI Lit reviews and bibliography, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Key literature on industry trends, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - New York film initiative, relations with clients, 2004-09 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - New media contacts, 2006-02-21 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Interviews NYFTCI, 2005-03-01 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - NYFTCI final report, notes and diagrams, 2005-08 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - New York NYFTCI presentation, 2004-12-04 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Technology, media, 2003-2005-10 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Production location trends, 2004-11-01-2005-09 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Media production trends, articles, 2003-07 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - ILR reports and data, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Summary reseach results, 2004-12 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - New York, varia from colleagues, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - NYFI literature review, 2001-2004 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Media industry reports, 2000-09-2002-03 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Report summaries, 2003-07-2004-10 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Media entertainment trends TV/Film, 2001-2005-11 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Commercial production, 2004-08-2005-11 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Media conglomerates, data, 2005-07-2005-11 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Media consolidation and labor, Undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - New York production history, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Strategies of US places to own production, 2004-01-23 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Assorted articles, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Freight and logistics, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Various notes, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Eds and Meds, and Metropolitan economic development, Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Transition and renewal: the emergence of a diverse upstate economy, 2004-01 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Various reports, 2001-2005 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Freight and transport related material, 2006-2007 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Brookings paper research, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Hollywood film industry, 2010-2011 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Organization and transformations of the international labor market, 1998-09-14 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Project contacts, mailing list, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - OECD connections, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Bibliography, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Articles about subsidies, 1997-2004 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Misc. new media and Silicon Valley material, 1996-1998 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Publications (Newsweek, Silicon Alley), 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Misc. material relating to cybernetics, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Writers Guild material, 1997-09-1998 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - New media collaborations, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - AEA report, 1998-06-08 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Entreprise zone expose Buffalo, 2003-06-09 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - 2nd New York new media industry survey, 1997-10 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Working partnership USA, 1997-08-1997-09 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - New media, lit review, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Interactive telecom program material, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - New media sources, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - New media, lit review, 1998 Spring (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Contingent labor policy studies, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Methodologies focus groups, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Industry breakdown, 1997-10-31 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Survey notes, 1994-1997 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - New York City interviews, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - New media, international contacts, 1999-01-31 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - New media theory, 1993-1998 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - International multimedia developments, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - The Warner annual report, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Writers' Guild of America member's handbook, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Art, culture, the changing economy, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Misc. publications, 1995-2005 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Subsidies paper revision, 2009-02 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Arts and culture in urban and regional planning manuscript, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Misc. journal articles, 2004-2009 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - JPER, film incentives, 2009-05 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Allen Scott review, 2005-08 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Film incentive book, Undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Christopherson articles, Undated (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Leeds paper CRESC, Undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - JPER, media paper NYC, 2006-11 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Creative after the crash, 2011-08 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Media work book proposal, Undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Subsidies, economic development quaterly, 2007-06 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Book with Charles Media, 2008-05 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Deuye Book paper, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Networking, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - New Media Study, Interviews, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - New York information sources, 2007-12-26 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Community audit methods, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - NYSAC Quaterly Reports, 2008-03-31 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary reports, 2008-08-06 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Bubble charts, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - New York stats for future proposals, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Location based awareness, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Industry partnerships, 2005-07-20-2008-03-04 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Powerpoints, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Background reports, 2003-2007 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Interview protocol, notes, 2008-10-14 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Grantmakers evaluation, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Benchmarking, indicators, 2007-10 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - ARS regional plans, 2007-10 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Pipeline 4 Progress report, 2007-12-24 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - R and D spillovers and geography of innovation and production, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Misc. notes and documents, Undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - CJE paper, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Service statistics, 1993-1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Annotated regional planning articles, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Regional studies essay, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Building regional economics through targeted workforce development, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Various annotated books (Box 14)
    - Regional resilience, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Notes, ideas, regional resilience, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Comparative research, anecdotal, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Firm Strategies, 1997-2005 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Proposals, 2005-06-2007-08-31 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Work plans, schedules, 2007-2008 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Arts and entertainment centre, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Barriers to regional workforce development strategies in "company towns": the Rochester Case, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - NYSAC contacts, 2008-08-06 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Local government leadership institute, 2009-08-13; CD-3848 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - NYSAC workforce intelligence project, 2005-2007 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Upstate New York development reports, 2000-2007 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Key studies, southern tier, 2006-2007 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - New York state economic growth, 2006-10-24-2006-11 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - NYSAC interviews, research and varia, 2006-10-2006-11 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Remaking book, marketing, Davidoff Award, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Series III. Produced work
  - International Economic Development Council Workforce Dev. Conf. Program, 2001-11-04-2001-11-06 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Sandercock-copyedited, 2000-03-20 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Fax of copyedits of SMC review of Sandercock book
  - Handbook for Teaching Assistants 1977, 1977-08 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Note on publication says "Won award from Fund for the Improvement of Post -Secondary Education"
  - Copies of publications, 1983-06 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Includes 'Female Labor Force…' published in Revista Geografica and 'The Household and Class Formation' from Environment and Planng D
  - Copies of publications, 1985-11 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Includes 'The Changing Organization and Location of the Motion Picture Industry' a report written with Michael Storper
  - Copies of publications, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Includes 'The City as Studio' (w/Michael Storper) and 'Household Structure and Activity in Ciudad Jurez' with Gay Young, published in 'The Social Ecology and Economic Development of Ciudad Jurez'
  - Copies of publications, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    Includes 'Flexible Specialization and Regional Industrial Agglomerations' (w/Michael Storper) and an issue of Planning, the magazine of the American Planning Assn. that features Storper and Christopherson's work
  - Copies of reports, conference papers, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Copies of reprints, articles, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Copies of CRP papers, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Copies of CRP papers, reports, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - The Origins of Fragmented Bargaining Power in Entertainment Media Industries, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Copies of an offprint from the IRRA Proceedings
  - Book review and report, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Copies of papers, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    Including 'International Journal of Urban and Regional Research' article, 'Market Rules and Territorial Outcomes,' and two conference proceedings from the United States Department of Agriculture, 'Rural America and the Changing Structure of Manufacturing' (other participants included Meric Gertler, Amy Glasmeier, Ed Malecki) and 'Population Change and the Future of Rural America' along with a cover letter for the latter document.
  - Industrial Development Agency (IDA) Accountablity in New York State, 1994-07 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Copy of a Community Development Research Brief
  - Drafts, reports, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    2nd draft of a manuscript entitled "Complicating Assumptions: Rules as Resources in Investment and Location Decisions," a draft paper for presentation at the Work Redesign and Work/Family Issues conference, sponsored by the Sloan Foundation and the Center on Work and Family at Boston University that features a discussion of restructuring at Cornell University (entitled The Gender Dimension of "Broad-Banding"), and a report for the United Nations Conference on Trade and Development entitled 'Current Developments and Trade Issues in Audio-Visual Services with Special Reference to the People's Republic of China'
  - Copies of papers and book chapters, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    Includes a short piece on Urban Theory from the newsletter of the Community and Urban Sociology Section of the American Sociological Association
  - Fast Money, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Materials including page proofs relating to the article 'Fast Money' SMC wrote with Rebecca Hovey
  - "Childcare and Elderly Care: What Occupational Opportunities for Women?", 1997 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Paper published by the OECD
  - Why Do National Labor Market Practices Continue to Diverge in a Global Economy?', 1998 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Prepared for U.S. Department of Labor, International Bureau of Labor Affairs in manuscript form and issued as a working paper by both the Cornell Institute for European Studies Working Paper and the University of Birmingham School of Geography Service Sector Research Unit
  - Manuscript for 'Rules for Resources', 1998 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Published in Barnes and Gertler (eds.), Regions, Regulation, and Institutions
  - Space, Society and Geographical Thought, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Japanese publication with translation of SMC's 'Flexibility in the US service economy'
  - Networking-EPI, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Publication by Rosemary Batt, SMC, Ned Righton, and Danielle Van Jaarvsveld for the Economic Policy Institute
  - Publications, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Copies of SMC articles published in Environment and Planning A (Project Work in Context) and Economic Geography ('Why Do National Labor Market Practices Continue to Diverge in the Global Economy? and a review of Place Matters)
  - Papers, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Manuscripts for two SMC papers: 'Can Walmartization be Stopped' and 'Divide and Conquer,' copy of SMC editorial from Geoforum-The limits to "New Regulation"-and report 'Optics, Imaging and Photonics'
  - Papers Publications Reports, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Copy of SMC article (The Divergent Worlds of New Media), manuscript (Neither Global Nor Standard), and reports ('Losing Ground' (w/Rolf Pendall), Transition and Renewal (w/Pendall and Matthew Drennan) [both for Brookings] and Final Report to the Department of Labor from the Rochester community audit
  - Publications and Reports, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Copy of SMC articles ('New Media After the Dot.Com Bust' [page proofs] and 'Behind the Scenes' as well as CRP-issued report that resulted from an economic development workshop entitled 'Taking Hold of the New Economy'
  - Book Review, 2007-01 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Review of Allen Scott's On Hollywood from 'Economic Geography'
  - Downsizing In America Review, 2004-11-29-2005-03 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, proof corrections and review of Baumol, Blinder and Wolff book for 'Urban Studies'
  - The Household and Class Formation, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Copy of SMC article from dissertation
  - Flexibility in the U.S. Service Economy, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Copy of SMC article
  - Fast Money article, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Copy of SMC article written with Rebecca Hovey
  - Divide and Conquer, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Copy of 'Divide and Conquer,' an essay published in 'Contracting Out Hollywood.'
  - Bennett Harrison's Gift, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Copy of short SMC piece reflecting on the life of Bennett Harrison, and published in Antipode
  - The Fortress City, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Copy of SMC book contribution from Amin, ed., The Post-Fordism: A Reader
  - Community Development Research Briefs, 1994-2001 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Research briefs, authored or coauthored by SMC and issued by the Cornell Community and Rural Development Institute. On looks at industrial development agencies and the other the Canal Corridor Initiative
  - High Technology in the Holy Land, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Copy of SMC book chapter (with Yehuda Gradus) that appeared in Muegge and Stoehr (eds.), International Economic Restructuring and the Regional Community
  - Market Rules and Territorial Outcomes, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Women's Waged Labor, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Copy of drafts of chapter included in Women, Work and Place, a book edited by Audrey Kobayashi
  - Women in the Arizona Economy, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Copy of SMC contribution to a report from the Southwest Institute for Research on Women, at the University of Arizona, Tucson
  - Double Jeopardy, 1985-1990 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    Copy of seemingly unpublished paper (not on 2002 cv): 'Double Jeopardy: The Consequences of Economic Adjustment For Rural Women,' from SMC time at the Southwest Instutute for Research on Women
  - The Mobile Workforce, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    Copy of SMC report prepared for The Roosevelt Center for Public Policy Research in Washington
  - The Path to Fragmented Bargaining Power, 1992-03 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    Copy of manuscript for a paper on entertainment industry
  - The False Promise of Industrial Districts for Rural Economic Development, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    SMC paper (with Beth Redfield), published in U.S. Department of Agriculture Conference Proceedings/U.S. Economics Research Service
  - SMC CVs, 1999-2002 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    Two cv's from various years, one, circa. 1999 or 2000, edited, the second from appx. 2002
  - Health Effects of Shale Gas Extraction Program, 2010-11-19 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    Conference program w/SMC participation
  - CDI Conference: Water Resources Infrastructure, 2014-09-17-2014-09-18 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    Conference program and notes for SMC panel presentation on water resources and economic viatlity
  - Peck Roepke Comm, 2015 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    Notes and draft response to Jamie Peck's 2015 Roepke Lecture at the AAG meetings. A more polished version would be published in 2016 in the journal Economic Geography (DOI: 10.1080/00130095.2015.1111754)
  - Reshoring Manufacturing, 2012 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    Contains an essay from Economic Developmentment Now June 18, 2012 by SMC and printout of slides from a presentation on the same topic (probably incomplete)
  - Brookings paper, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Secretary's commission of workforce equality and labor market efficiency (US Dept. of Labor), 1988-10-17 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Drafts and Brookings paper, 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Drafts, Undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Brookings paper version, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - WIAL paper draft freight, 2009-01-13 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Freight transportation and economic development material, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Oxford handbook material, 2016 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Ideas for regional resilience book, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Gary Gereffi, 2005-10-28 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Book cover proofs, remaking regional economies, Undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - New York's big picture: assessing New York's position in film, television, and commercial production, 2006-08 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Chistopherson, Rule as, 1995-12 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Labor flexibility stats. Comparative paper, 1995-08 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Labor flexibility clippings, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Flexibility papers, misc. notes, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - SMC contributors, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Extending the institutional turn, draft, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - OTA labor flexibility study, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Publishing agreement and varia, 2015 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - OIR paper, notes with Jennifer, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Smith foundation piece, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Manufacturing matters notes, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Phoenix industry cases, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Phoenix literature review, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Syracuse interviews, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Articles and notes on regional economy, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Chapter one, introduction, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Understanding governance, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Introduction to market rules book, 1998-06 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Book proposal, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Published work and notes, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Media paper draft, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Media work paper research, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Media work articles, 2000-2008 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - OECD theme paper, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Phoenix industries readings, Undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Manchester piece, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Outline for workshop on planner's grant, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Resilience, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Transport papers, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - OIR notes from 2010 AAG meeting, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Phoenix workplan, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Misc. clippings, 2004-2012 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Regional resilience, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Washington talk ideas, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Assorted SMC Publications, 1973-2014 (Box 17)
    Unsorted copies of her publications--Note that there is no physical folder named "Assorted SMC Publications"
  - Assorted SMC Publications, 1989-2010 (Box 18)
- Series IV. Correspondence
  - Cail, Krys Emails, 2000-09-29-2000-21-07 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Perkins, James Email, 2000-08-29 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Pendall, Rolf Email, 2000-09-29 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Rearden, Ken, 2000-10-11 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Letter from Prof. Ken Reardon to Robert Giloth (Senior Program Officer at Annie E. Casey Foundation) detailing conversations they had (SMC and Pierre Clavel) regarding Annie E. Casey Foundation funding three CRP projects
  - Conversation Finkel, 2016-01-27-2016-01-30 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Letter from SMC to the deputy editor of Energy and Environment proposing an article (coauthored with Madelon Finkel) on the "environmental and public health risks of the foot print of shale gas and oil development in the US" and the editor, Martin La Monica's reply.
  - Communications G. LeRoy, etc., 1993-1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)